graphicleftovers.com 2009-12-27

# Privacy Policy - Graphic Leftovers

Our privacy policy

Your privacy is very important to us. Graphic Leftovers ("Administrator") adheres to the following privacy policy regarding its collection, use and dissemination of personal and non-personal information collected through its website ("Site"). Administrator reserves the right to modify its privacy policy at any time.

Collection of Non-Personal Information  
Whenever you visit a web page on the internet, your browser automatically identifies the IP address from where your page request was initiated – i.e. your computer. It also volunteers certain basic information like browser type, the operating system you are running, and in some cases the page which referred to the Site (if you clicked a link from another website). The Administrator's server automatically collects this information and tracks it on a page by page and on a statistical basis.

**Use of Non-Personal Information**  
The Administrator uses non-personal information such as the region or country your IP request came from to suggest the appropriate language to use or to select the best presentation aligned to that region of the world. We also use browser type, operating system, and page visits for statistical analysis of site usage and navigation trends.

Collection of Personal Information  
When you sign up as an Adopter or Promoter under the relevant agreement, we may ask for your name, your e-mail address, and contact information. The Administrator also uses "Cookies" to collect information about our visitors.

Use and Disclosure of Personal Information  
We maintain this information for statistical purposes to improve our Site and the Materials (as defined in the “Site Terms of Use”), to administer the Site, and to communicate with users and.The Administrator will not give or sell this information to third parties for any purpose other than to assist us in providing information to you or to manage and improve the Site and Materials. The Administrator will also respond to legal requests for information where required by law to do so.

External Links  
The Site may contain links to third party sites. Since the Administrator does not control those websites, we encourage you to review the privacy policies of these third party sites.

Security  
Access to your information is limited to the Administrator's employees and our service providers who we believe have a justified business reason to access your information. All information is protected through password access and only to identified corporate users.
